One dream,
one wish If you want it,
gotta go over the top!
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marks maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
I still can't believe this.
It's not fair!
Komurasaki, why?
What I wouldn't give to see her once more!
I guess this is the
Oidon's final procession.
Where are you taking her?
She belongs in the capital with us.
She rebelled against Shogun Orochi.
We'll cremate her at the prisoners'
quarters in Rosetsu Town.
They captured him? That was sudden.
I have no idea what's going on anymore.
That Tonoyasu guy is Ushimitsu Koza?
He didn't strike me as a thief.
But if the rumors are true, our new
friend is quite the influential figure.
He robs from the rich, a hero who
gives to the poor and powerless.
So you're telling me that
guy's a secret badass?
Ushimitsu Koza.
I heard that name over and
over in the flower capital.
They called him a saint.
Maybe he really is a hero.
It's a live projection.
Why is everyone laughing at him?
Your friend's getting strung up.
Show some sympathy.
You still find it hard to
believe that he's Ushimitsu Koza.
It could be a lie.
But for right now,
that's hardly the issue.
It's coming back to me.
I could never forget that heir.
Tonoyasu is merely an alias.
What has this guy been hiding?
A lot of buzz going on
in the capital today.
I'd better tune in.
Someone turn on the light scroll, Snail.
Is that guy someone you know?
Of course he's quite famous.
Back in my day, he was a
daimyo under the Kozuki clan.
That's to say, he was a
close associate of Lord Odin.
Shimutsuki Yasui.
That's his name.
Sir Yasui!
The daimyo of Hakumai—that's Yasuie,
the hedgehog—known for his austerity.
He was famous for rarely smiling.
If you can believe it,
even as he stood right before
me, I failed to recognize him.
recognize him Stop the execution!
Olive Hakamai still loves you!
I thought you were gone!
Untie him, you monsters!
Lord Yasui!
They didn't forget about
me after all this time!
Ain't that sweet?
Hakumai holds a unique
position in the land of Wano,
in that it is the only region
with a legitimate port.
Some visitors wish us well,
but others wish us harm.
The course is clear.
Our army must be an unassailable force!
Without a doubt, you've got the
strongest samurai in the land of Wano.
Wanna buy it?
This is no time to fool
around, Odin. Wake up!
How long are you going to loiter here?
You realize that you're the son of
the shogun, not some hapless vagrant?
I'm afraid I was kicked out of the castle.
I might have been kicked out
of the family for that matter.
Surely you've heard the talk people say:
"odin will never be heir
to kozuki." Hey, Sukiyaki.
Yasui will become the Shogun.
You idiot!
Ouch!
What was that for?
Don't put so much stock in idle chatter.
You're the true successor of the
Kozuki clan, beyond any doubt.
Lord Tsukiyaki only kicked you out because
he loves you and wants you to learn.
You should try to meet his expectations.
Maybe so.
But frankly, if I had it my
way, I'd rather go out to sea.
Just my luck living in a
country with closed borders.
This isolation policy is
such a pain in the ass.
Watch your mouth!
Until you're a proper samurai, you've
no right to criticize this land.
That won't hurt, you know.
You can't just keep knocking
me around like that.
Who do you think I am?
Right now, a nobody.
A mere hoodlum.
Sorry, everyone.
It's no use.
There's no way Orochi
is going to let me go.
First, I want to apologize for two things.
Then I'd like to say something
to that moron Orochi.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Chaka!
Once I get that off my chest,
I can head to the great beyond
with a smile on my face.
Ah.
Attention!
I will now read the
charges of the accused.
Last night, he was caught committing
a theft in the flower capital.
A shameless sycophant,
this former daimyo of
Hakubai has been reduced
to begging for coin as
a lowly entertainer.
His name is Shimotsuki Yasui.
He once committed the heinous crime of
rebelling against the shogun Orochi.
He will serve as an offering on this day
of the Oiran Gomorrah Saki's funeral.
We hereby sentence him
to a dishonorable death.
Now,
according to his statement,
he is also the serial
thief Ushimitsu Koza,
who is a well-known public
menace in the capital.
Now that was a lie!
A lie?
But why would you say that?
Figured I might as well grab all your
attention one last time, since I'm gonna die!
I'm sorry for laughing, you guys!
I'm flattered you thought
I was a hero, though!
I don't understand.
Yes, it is perplexing.
Well, Yasui got the attention he wanted.
The uproar surrounding the Oedon's
funeral has been redirected to him.
Drake, sir!
The people of Evisu Town are rioting!
They're charging into the
flower capital in droves!
They're what?
We've made an error.
We underestimated how important
this man was to the common people.
Don't you go dyin' on us, Yasuie!
We're coming for you, just wait!
If they don't have you to support us,
we'll be dead and rotting in a week!
Go back to Ebisu Town, you beggars!
You're not allowed to enter here!
Stand down!
Yasuie!
The crowds on the main
street are running wild!
In the West District, too!
It's one thing after another.
In retrospect,
Lord Orochi's decision to
broadcast the execution through
the light scrolls may have
been somewhat short-sighted.
Let's keep an eye on
the other areas as well.
I can't help but feel sorry
for the Shogun's poor flunkies!
Must not be easy working for a damn idiot!
Attention, if you would, please!
Gaze upon the beauty
of the flower capital.
Our land of Wano shines brightly.
This nation is our pride and joy.
For it was won by generations
of hard work by the Kozuki clan.
and the people who supported them.
Faster!
Hurry up!
I don't want that bastard running
his mouth a second longer!
This is not your doing in the
least, you greedy old snake!
You hear me, Kurosamine Orochi?
You haven't built an inch of this land.
All you've done is polluted
our fields and forests,
our rivers,
our villages.
All of their splendor has
been tainted by your greed.
You're nothing but famine.
How dare you.
I'll kill you for this.
You think you can set fire to my home.
And not suffer the consequences.
Where are you?
Fight me!
Hold on.
It can't be?
It's all right.
You said more than enough.
Don't make the Shogun angry, please!
There's something else I should add.
Another apology while I
still have the chance.
It's about the flyer with the symbol
that's been going around lately.
The Kozuki name died out 20 years ago.
I couldn't form an army
to avenge them if I tried.
But I don't want people to forget them.
That's why I made that flyer!
The symbol doesn't mean anything at all.
It's just a prank.
At all the cheese expense!
Oh, why would he say that?
There you are, Ashura.
So it's you, did you see?
I was shocked.
Look, at least Lord Yasui's
alive for the time being.
I saw, though I was late to
find out just as you were.
It's become quite the spectacle.
When Lord Odin died 20 years back,
Odin asked the four remaining
Damiel, including myself, a question.
Would we serve under the
Karotsumi clan or fight them?
What a laugh!
You owed everything you had to Odin,
but you stole the Shogun's throne
out from under him with deceit.
and treachery, what fool would serve you?
The daimyo and people from every region
raised up their swords without hesitation.
But we were no match for that monster
Kaido who crushed all opposition.
And the Lamb of Wano paid the price.
Alas, I lost my chance to
die with honor in that fight.
So I took on a disguise and hid.
But I would be ashamed if I died
of old age, living this lie.
So, channeling my inner child,
I came up with this flyer trick
as a final act of rebellion.
If you would forgive this
old fool, but you know,
turns out Orji was a bigger
coward than I ever imagined.
He got so spooked by the whole thing that
he jailed innocent
people just because they
followed a stylish little trend.
So it was all in his head this whole time?
What should we do?
We're locked away a ton of people!
Almost there, Lord Orochi!
Yasui!
You've said enough!
I'm about to pump you full of lead!
There you are!
Haven't seen you in ages, Orochi!
If you have any more last
words, save them fast!
Alright, let me see.
Would you like me to recite
the poem that binds your heart?
A man of such small
caliber shall never know
the taste of Odin for as
long as he shall live.
Looks like this is it for me.
Kin'emon and the rest of the Akataya
Samurai, you know what to do.
And Momonosuke, I know
you'll be Shogun someday.
Your plan has not been undone.
It has merely been reset.
Your allies in Rosetsu
Town have not been lost.
I gave them a new rendezvous point.
It may not be much, but this is all
I can do with what's left of my life.
I feel we're helpless to stop this.
It seems he's sacrificing
himself to keep our plan alive.
There is nothing more I can say.
Thank you, my friend.
Now, no matter what that coward
or what she goes on about,
his soldiers won't listen to him anymore.
I'm getting real sick of
the Shogun's paranoia.
You can't say that out loud!
Daddy!
Yasuie!
For 20 long years, we
bowed our heads in shame.
For what could we do
before the might of Kaido?
But this time, things will be different.
Cover your children's eyes! For now,
the final Dome to serve Kozuki, or rather,
the happy-go-lucky fool from Evisutown.
makes his final journey!
Yasui!
I think I'll go out singing.
Here we go.
Fire.
Oh, Kakarone Gashima, avenge
your lord at long last.
I shall await the good
news in the next world.
What were you thinking, trying
to steal all this money,
Lord Odin was running short on cash, okay.
If you're gonna kill us, then
do it, you damn hedgehog!
What a mess!
Where do you find these people, Odin?
Listen up, you tried to steal my
money, but I'll let you keep it. Huh?
Wado?
Please reconsider, Lord Yasui.
Hakumai needs those funds
much more than they do.
I don't care.
While we're at it, here's a bit more.
Take it.
Even more money?
There's a catch, right?
What is this, a trap?
Do you truly love Odin?
Are you joking?
Of course we do.
I owe him my life.
Yeah, what he said.
I see.
In that case, use this money
to clean yourselves up.
Buy some books.
Learn some manners.
Get educated.
Having a bunch of unruly thugs as
vassals will only bring shame to Odin.
One day, I'm sure, he will become
the Shogun of the land of Wano.
Therefore, those who support
him must not only be loyal,
they must be the finest
samurai in the country.
It goes without saying that
you must protect your lord.
But the people of Wano will
come to depend on you as well.
You must be a symbol of our
strength, our guardian deities.
Understood?
Sir Yasui!
Daddy! Daddy!
I'm coming!
Daddy!
Otoko.
I'm so sorry, Otoko.
It looks like I'll be leaving you behind.
Daddy!
Daddy! Daddy!
Enough!
You may cease firing!
Yasuie!
It's those beggars from Ebisu Town.
Kick them out of the capital!
Yasuie!
Sir Yasui!
Nya!
Please don't die!
Daddy, no!
No!
Yasuie!
Is that damn rat finally dead?
Lord Yasuie is gone!
I don't know.
What the hell's going on here?
Yeah.
Everyone's laughing.
Somebody just died.
Do you think that this is a joke?
My daddy is dead!
You little brat!
Please, wait!
The truth is, they are all crying.
Crying?
The people from Ebizu
Town are always smiling.
Because even when they're hurting or
sad, they can't show it on their faces.
Even if they're suffering, they've been
robbed of everything but their smiles.
Now, all they can do is laugh.
Kaido and Orochi, they
brought something here.
It's an evil fruit that they call Smile.